hi guys good day everyone it's your
mommy lori here and welcome to my
channel
so today's vlog guys i'm a greedy
beautiful
handheld steamer nana bilina means
costco a few weeks ago
[Music]
and nothing
steamer
[Music]
and easy to remove
it
[Music]
or fabrics
last but not the least is the third
attachment the steam bonnet
[Music]
yeah
so you need steam bonuses
if you want to prevent the steam
from
falling to the garments that we are
[Music]
you
is about
one cup of
water or 250 ml
madeline
just push
and you hear the click and it's already
secured then into your power button here
you
red side is
delicate sorry blue paladin delicate
and then new
red side
[Music]
is
until in
[Music]
and in the first
few minutes
[Music]
to use nasha you can switch it up to
delicate or turbo
and then once that you
are not using it
just
press it
hold it
and then it will turn off
blue light giant
and then make sure
you will store away
for uh
[Music]
make sure not empty not in young
ready
[Music]
that means our
steamer is ready for use
against the next apple in less than a
minute let's start now by
mixtape
so you see here you blue button if you
use a delicate
and once you press the other button to
the
right
this is now the folder
[Music]
steam continuing steam
yeah
so
up and down motion lamp
yeah
[Music]
guys
as long as in the
industry wrinkled or wrinkly
[Music]
i am guess
putting
[Music]
foreign
is
[Music]
um
so thank you guys for watching and
tuning in to my video
and i hope you guys have a wonderful day
and if you haven't subscribed to my
channel yet please subscribe
to mommy glory and hit the subscribe
button below this video and to stay
updated
with my new uploads please click also
the bell icon
thank you so much
[Music]
you